wisestep.com 2011-11-24

# Privacy Policy

At WiseStep.com we know that you care how information about you is used and shared; Your privacy is important to us. The details below allow you to learn more about how your information is used and with whom it is shared and so on  
WiseStep.com is a network of Professionals connecting with each other or their friends, to share opportunities in business, career, knowledge and other professional or social areas. When you open an account with us, you provide personally identifiable information. 

**A. Information Collected  
**  
1\. To become a WiseStep.com member, you must open an account yourself or at the request of an existing member. To open an account you are required to provide the following mandatory information: name, email address, country, industry, Postal code and a password. 

2\. You can create your own profile page that has information on your education, work experience and share it with the other members. You can choose to display the information you want to, to other members of the site by modifying your profile settings. WiseStep.com will use this information to customize your experience on the web site. For example, when you login to your account we will display the new users who have joined the network. Similarly job opportunities that are new on the website may be shown to you.

3\. To Invite others to connect with you directly on WiseStep.com, you can either invite them directly if you know their email addresses or if they are already existing members of WiseStep.com you can get introduced to them through other members. This information will be used by WiseStep.com to send your invitation including a message that you write. The names and email addresses of people that you invite will be used only to send your invitation and reminders. WiseStep.com may choose to remind some of the users of any pending request that is initiated by other members on the website. You may also choose to Import contacts from your other email providers or networking communities. All information imported will only be viewable by you and will not be searchable by others in the WiseStep.com network. None of your friends will be contacted or sent emails until you decide to invite them. 

4\. All information that you enter or import about your contacts will be covered by the same terms of this privacy policy as it covers your own personally identifiable information.

5\. WiseStep.com provides specific areas on the website where external weblinks may appear. WiseStep.com does not endorse these websites but these websites may choose to customize the links shown on WiseStep.com depending on their customization of weblinks based on the WiseStep.com professional community.

**B. Cookies & Web Logs   
**  
WiseStep.com uses cookies and web log files to track site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file which resides on your computer which allows WiseStep.com to recognize you as a user when you return to our site using the same computer and web browser. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to use our website. Like the information you enter at registration or in your Profile, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on the web site.  
One type of cookie, known as a "persistent" cookie, is set once you have logged in to your WiseStep.com account. The next time you visit the WiseStep.com web site, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as an existing user so you will not need to log in before using the service. Additionally, if you log out of the WiseStep.com site you will need to re-enter your password the next time you visit in order to log in to your account. Another type of cookie, called a "session" cookie, is used to identify a particular visit to the WiseStep.com site. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser.

Due to the communications standards on the Internet, when you visit the WiseStep.com web site we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave WiseStep.com. We also receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, as well as the name of your ISP. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the WiseStep.com service. The linkage between your IP address and your personally identifiable information is never shared with third-parties without your permission or except when required by law.

**C. Information Sharing  
**  
1\. 

_Information Use:_

**WiseStep.com is an online service dedicated to help professionals in effectively connecting with one another. The personally identifiable information you choose to provide on this site is used to help you describe yourself to other users. Other information, that does not personally identify you as an individual, is collected by WiseStep.com from the site (such as, by way of example, patterns of utilization) and is exclusively owned by WiseStep.com. This information can be utilized by WiseStep.com in such manner as WiseStep.com, in its sole discretion, deems appropriate**

2\. 

_Sharing Information with Third Parties:_

At WiseStep.com the privacy of your information is important to us 

1\. We will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third party for marketing purposes. 

2\. We will only share your personally identifiable information with third parties to carry out your instructions and to provide specific services. 

3\. These third parties do not retain, share, or store any personally identifiable information except to provide these services and are bound by strict confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information. 

WiseStep.com offers a "public profile" feature which allows users to publish portions of their WiseStep.com profile, including your "name", but not your other profile information. Users can choose to set their own preferences from the settings section and may opt-out of this feature; however WiseStep.com does not warrant how third-parties search engines will update their cache if the information is made public and then restricted by members at a later date.  
We may provide aggregated data about the usage of our services to third-parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate. We may segment our members using different criteria that is considered standard in marketing and market research or other criteria at our sole discretion

We will transfer information about you if WiseStep.com enters a joint venture or is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, WiseStep.com will notify you by email or by informing members on the web site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

4\. Communications between Users:

Many communications or messages that you initiate through WiseStep.com, will list your email address and name in the header of the message. Emails you initiate may also provide aggregate information about your network (for instance how many people are in your network), but will never list the people to whom you are directly connected. Other communications that you initiate through the WiseStep.com website, like a request for contact, will list your name as the initiator but will not include your personal contact information. Your contact information will only be shared with another user if both of you have indicated that you would like to establish contact with each other.

5\. Legal Disclaimer:

It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on our company or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

**D. External Links**

WiseStep.com may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by WiseStep.com.

**E. WiseStep.com Communications**

WiseStep.com will communicate with you through email and messages posted on this website. These include a series of welcome, reminder emails which help and inform new and old users about various features of the service. Please be aware that you will always receive certain emails from WiseStep.com related to the proper functioning of your account, such as email notices when another user in your network sends you an opportunity. WiseStep.com may send you promotional information unless you have opted out of receiving such information. If you wish to opt-out of receiving promotional emails, please send a request to support@WiseStep.com

**F. Accessing and Changing Your Account Information**

You can review the personal information you provided us and make any desired changes to the information, or to the settings for your WiseStep.com account, at any time by logging in to your account on the WiseStep.com website and editing the information on your Profile page. You can close your account through the WiseStep.com website or by writing to us at support@WiseStep.com . If you close your WiseStep.com account, we will remove your name and other personally identifiable information from our publicly viewable data. We may retain certain data contributed by you if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. All retained data will continue to be subject to the terms of the WiseStep.com Privacy Policy that you have previously agreed to. To close your account and remove your information from the WiseStep.com service, please send your request to support@WiseStep.com Please send your request using the email account that you have registered with WiseStep.com under your name. You will receive a response to requests sent to support@WiseStep.com ithin five business days of our receiving it.

**G. Security**

In order to secure your personal information, access to your data on WiseStep.com is password-protected. To protect any data you store on our servers we also regularly audit our system for possible vulnerabilities and attacks and we use a tier-one secured-access data center.

**H. Changes**

WiseStep.com may update this privacy policy. In the event there are significant changes in the way we treat your personally identifiable information, we will display a notice on this site. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. Notice of all changes that materially affects the way in which your personally identifiable data may be used or shared will be posted in updates to our privacy policy. If you continue to use the WiseStep.com service after notice of changes has been sent or published on our site, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices.

**I. Questions or Comments**

If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, please contact support@WiseStep.com
